<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <title>Phoenix&#39;s Blog</title>
  
  
  <link href="http://example.com/atom.xml" rel="self"/>
  
  <link href="http://example.com/"/>
  <updated>2022-01-29T17:13:27.236Z</updated>
  <id>http://example.com/</id>
  
  <author>
    <name>Phoenix</name>
    
  </author>
  
  <generator uri="https://hexo.io/">Hexo</generator>
  
  <entry>
    <title></title>
    <link href="http://example.com/2022/01/29/Genshin/"/>
    <id>http://example.com/2022/01/29/Genshin/</id>
    <published>2022-01-29T17:13:27.236Z</published>
    <updated>2022-01-29T17:13:27.236Z</updated>
    
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<h1 id="The-best-ratio-between-CRIT-rate-and-CRIT-damage-in-Genshin-Impact-updating"><a href="#The-best-ratio-between-CRIT-rate-and-CRIT-damage-in-Genshin-Impact-updating" class="headerlink" title="The best ratio between CRIT rate and CRIT damage in Genshin Impact(updating)"></a>The best ratio between CRIT rate and CRIT damage in Genshin Impact(updating)</h1><h2 id="1-ABSTRACT"><a href="#1-ABSTRACT" class="headerlink" title="1. ABSTRACT"></a>1. ABSTRACT</h2><p>  This article was only researched the best ratio of CRIT rate (record as p) and CRIT damage(record as r), which means ignoring the influence of  ATK, element mastery, etc.  Actually,  the other factors may have a higher damage yield than CRIT sometimes, therefore, the result does not talk about the priority of each factor.  Moreover, we considered the single character without any buffs and the effect of the individual operation. </p><p>  In players’ consciousness, CRIT rate : CRIT damage = 1 : 2can gain the maximum damage expectation which is an experienced conclusion. However, it only was appropriate for multiple attacks. the actual damage will be deflected when the attack times decreased. So,Ii converted the expectation to two meaningful points</p><ol><li><em>the time you need to complete the challenge</em>(in the domain battle)</li><li><em>the number of times you need to complete the challenge</em> (in the spiral abyss)</li></ol><p>  Someone may say, the high DPS, the lower time you need. The higher CRIT damage, the greater opportunities to overcome the challenge. BUT I wanted to find accurate and quantitative relations between them, even some of results were against common sense OR looks unnecessary. </p>]]></content>
    
    
      
      
    <summary type="html">&lt;h1 id=&quot;The-best-ratio-between-CRIT-rate-and-CRIT-damage-in-Genshin-Impact-updating&quot;&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;#The-best-ratio-between-CRIT-rate-and-CRIT-dam</summary>
      
    
    
    
    
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title>Hello World</title>
    <link href="http://example.com/2022/01/29/hello-world/"/>
    <id>http://example.com/2022/01/29/hello-world/</id>
    <published>2022-01-29T17:13:27.236Z</published>
    <updated>2022-01-29T17:13:27.236Z</updated>
    
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>Welcome to <a class="link"   href="https://hexo.io/" >Hexo<i class="fas fa-external-link-alt"></i></a>! This is your very first post. Check <a class="link"   href="https://hexo.io/docs/" >documentation<i class="fas fa-external-link-alt"></i></a> for more info. If you get any problems when using Hexo, you can find the answer in <a class="link"   href="https://hexo.io/docs/troubleshooting.html" >troubleshooting<i class="fas fa-external-link-alt"></i></a> or you can ask me on <a class="link"   href="https://github.com/hexojs/hexo/issues" >GitHub<i class="fas fa-external-link-alt"></i></a>.</p><h2 id="Quick-Start"><a href="#Quick-Start" class="headerlink" title="Quick Start"></a>Quick Start</h2><h3 id="Create-a-new-post"><a href="#Create-a-new-post" class="headerlink" title="Create a new post"></a>Create a new post</h3><figure class="highlight bash"><table><tr><td class="gutter"><pre><span class="line">1</span><br></pre></td><td class="code"><pre><span class="line">$ hexo new <span class="string">&quot;My New Post&quot;</span></span><br></pre></td></tr></table></figure><p>More info: <a class="link"   href="https://hexo.io/docs/writing.html" >Writing<i class="fas fa-external-link-alt"></i></a></p><h3 id="Run-server"><a href="#Run-server" class="headerlink" title="Run server"></a>Run server</h3><figure class="highlight bash"><table><tr><td class="gutter"><pre><span class="line">1</span><br></pre></td><td class="code"><pre><span class="line">$ hexo server</span><br></pre></td></tr></table></figure><p>More info: <a class="link"   href="https://hexo.io/docs/server.html" >Server<i class="fas fa-external-link-alt"></i></a></p><h3 id="Generate-static-files"><a href="#Generate-static-files" class="headerlink" title="Generate static files"></a>Generate static files</h3><figure class="highlight bash"><table><tr><td class="gutter"><pre><span class="line">1</span><br></pre></td><td class="code"><pre><span class="line">$ hexo generate</span><br></pre></td></tr></table></figure><p>More info: <a class="link"   href="https://hexo.io/docs/generating.html" >Generating<i class="fas fa-external-link-alt"></i></a></p><h3 id="Deploy-to-remote-sites"><a href="#Deploy-to-remote-sites" class="headerlink" title="Deploy to remote sites"></a>Deploy to remote sites</h3><figure class="highlight bash"><table><tr><td class="gutter"><pre><span class="line">1</span><br></pre></td><td class="code"><pre><span class="line">$ hexo deploy</span><br></pre></td></tr></table></figure><p>More info: <a class="link"   href="https://hexo.io/docs/one-command-deployment.html" >Deployment<i class="fas fa-external-link-alt"></i></a></p>]]></content>
    
    
      
      
    <summary type="html">&lt;p&gt;Welcome to &lt;a class=&quot;link&quot;   href=&quot;https://hexo.io/&quot; &gt;Hexo&lt;i class=&quot;fas fa-external-link-alt&quot;&gt;&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/a&gt;! This is your very first post. Che</summary>
      
    
    
    
    
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title></title>
    <link href="http://example.com/2022/01/29/probe1/"/>
    <id>http://example.com/2022/01/29/probe1/</id>
    <published>2022-01-29T17:13:27.236Z</published>
    <updated>2022-01-29T17:13:27.236Z</updated>
    
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p><strong>Q1.Why do you want to study that subject and what evidence do you have that your interest is real and not superficial?</strong></p><p>To be honest, I want to devote myself into the computer science in the future, especially on hardware. You probably don’t know I am a big fan of e-game such as league of legend. Moreover, I really care about the graphic. However, while the quality of game improved, the development of hardware is really slow in contrast. Hence, some people who like me cannot afford the high-end equipment have an awful experience when we play the latest game or even cannot play. So, in the future, I would like to create the hardware which is both economical and high efficiency.</p><p><strong>Q2.Where do you want to study and why?</strong></p><p>Personally speaking, I would like to study with my classmate in a quiet place. Attention that I don’t mean the library although somebody may say it is easy for us to search materials. However, With the several decades development of internet, it is much convenient for us to find essay, website, journal and so on. In addition, you also can read the book in the library on the site.</p><p>When I face some problems, I will discuss with outstanding students or together. Furthermore, we will ensure all of us understand. I really enjoy in this atmosphere.</p><p><strong>Q3.What do you know about the skills and attributes that the admissions tutor is looking for and how will you convince them that you possess these key skills?</strong></p><p>Leadership(makes everybody better, take responsibility), creativity(introduce my design), problem solving(design an appropriate solution, put it in effective use), critical thinking, communication(face to face &amp; medium), collaboration(teamwork), information management(find the source or answer quickly), adaptability, curiosity(ask teachers), reflection(make summary)</p><p><strong>Q4.What evidence can you provide that supports your interest? This evidence must be more than just a list of what you have done at A level.</strong></p><p>In fact, I am interested in computer science and physics. I usually learn knowledge from internet especially the comment about the hardware such as CPU and Graphic Card. In addition, in the summer holiday, I completed a meaningful program which constructed a NAS(Network Attached Storage) server and solve the problems of photo storage.</p><p>For physics, I spent a large number of time to steep in it. For example, I had studied the AS physics by myself in this summer holiday. I also learn something about physics competition and I will join the BPho in November. </p><p><strong>Q5.What do admissions tutors in your area of interest look for in a good statement?</strong></p><p>Why are me applying foe my chosen course?</p><p>Evidence that I understand what’s required to study the course.</p><p>Why I suitable for the course?</p><p>Any particular skills and experience that will help me to succeed on the courses.</p><p>The activities that demonstrate my interest in the course.</p><p>List of hobbies, skills and abilities.</p><p>Work experience includes details of jobs, placements, work experience.</p><p>Link skills or qualities relate to the course.</p><p>Why I choose UK</p><p>My future plan</p><p><strong>Q6.What have your studies so far taught you about the course you hope to apply for – for instance, if applying to read Chemistry, what have you done at A level or equivalent that sparked your interest?</strong></p><p>Well, I apply for physics because I find my talent when I studied. I can solve the problem much quicker than peers and I even can deduce some simple formula by myself.</p><p>Computer science – as I mention, I had a terrible experience of playing computer game. I want to improve the hardware and optimize the game</p>]]></content>
    
    
      
      
    <summary type="html">&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Q1.Why do you want to study that subject and what evidence do you have that your interest is real and not superficial?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/</summary>
      
    
    
    
    
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title></title>
    <link href="http://example.com/2022/01/29/%E6%96%87%E4%B9%A6/"/>
    <id>http://example.com/2022/01/29/%E6%96%87%E4%B9%A6/</id>
    <published>2022-01-29T17:13:27.236Z</published>
    <updated>2022-01-29T17:13:27.236Z</updated>
    
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<h1 id="Application-Essay-paragraph-2"><a href="#Application-Essay-paragraph-2" class="headerlink" title="Application Essay(paragraph 2)"></a>Application Essay(paragraph 2)</h1><h4 id="Briefly-describe-a-personal-goal-you-have-set-for-yourself-and-how-long-you-have-been-working-to-achieve-this-goal-Who-did-you-turn-to-for-advice-or-help-and-what-was-their-role-what-did-you-learn-about-yourself-maximum-350-words"><a href="#Briefly-describe-a-personal-goal-you-have-set-for-yourself-and-how-long-you-have-been-working-to-achieve-this-goal-Who-did-you-turn-to-for-advice-or-help-and-what-was-their-role-what-did-you-learn-about-yourself-maximum-350-words" class="headerlink" title="Briefly describe a personal goal you have set for yourself, and how long you have been working to achieve this goal. Who did you turn to for advice or help, and what was their role? what did you learn about yourself? (maximum 350 words)"></a><em>Briefly describe a personal goal you have set for yourself, and how long you have been working to achieve this goal. Who did you turn to for advice or help, and what was their role? what did you learn about yourself? (maximum 350 words)</em></h4><p>Last term, I realized that my English level was awful, and that this was affecting my school assignments and exam results. Therefore, through discussion with my English teacher at the parents’ meeting. I set up an appropriate goal in which I would aim to get a “B” grade in my final exam.</p><p>The process of working towards my goal was more arduous than I initially thought. Firstly, the remaining time was too short for me—only three months which meant that I had to start working as soon as possible. Secondly, considering that I did not want to fall behind in my other subjects including my IELTS preparation, I had no choice but to squeeze the necessary extra work into my daily life. Hence, my father and I modified my original work schedule in order to make my goal more reasonable and achievable. During this period, my father often reminded me of deadlines associated with essential matters such as my mock exam. He also taught me how to write a feasible plan. In spite of this help, there were still many setbacks during the process.</p><p>In addition, there were some problems with my oral test too. For instance ,I would often feel nervous when I talked with the examiner. As a result, I was often unable to speak to the examiner. Although I felt familiar with the words, I still forgot them during the test. Moreover, I could not find any resources to help me with the test. Both of these issues made me anxious nearly all term. The only solution that my English teacher offered was practicing more. Thus, I often chatted with my friends in English in class or even in daily life. Unexpectedly, our teachers then set up speaking lessons to improve our ability.</p><p>On balance, I have understood that study by myself not only requires hard work but also others’ help. Although the result of the examination is not yet known, I am full of self-confidence and am not feeling stressed. </p>]]></content>
    
    
      
      
    <summary type="html">&lt;h1 id=&quot;Application-Essay-paragraph-2&quot;&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;#Application-Essay-paragraph-2&quot; class=&quot;headerlink&quot; title=&quot;Application Essay(paragraph 2)&quot;&gt;&lt;/</summary>
      
    
    
    
    
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title></title>
    <link href="http://example.com/2022/01/29/%E6%96%87%E4%B9%A6%E7%AC%AC%E4%B8%89%E6%AE%B5/"/>
    <id>http://example.com/2022/01/29/%E6%96%87%E4%B9%A6%E7%AC%AC%E4%B8%89%E6%AE%B5/</id>
    <published>2022-01-29T17:13:27.236Z</published>
    <updated>2022-01-29T17:13:27.236Z</updated>
    
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<h2 id="Describe-an-accomplishment-event-or-realization-that-sparked-a-period-of-personal-growth-and-a-new-understanding-of-yourself-or-others-Maximum-350-words"><a href="#Describe-an-accomplishment-event-or-realization-that-sparked-a-period-of-personal-growth-and-a-new-understanding-of-yourself-or-others-Maximum-350-words" class="headerlink" title="Describe an accomplishment, event, or realization that sparked a period of personal growth and a new understanding of yourself or others.  (Maximum 350 words)"></a>Describe an accomplishment, event, or realization that sparked a period of personal growth and a new understanding of yourself or others.  (Maximum 350 words)</h2><p>When I began high school in 2020, it was immediately apparent that it is almost impossible for me to ensure the similar rank as before because it would were outstanding students in our previous school. Moreover, my classmates were more indifferent than my junior high school classmates and as a result, there was little communications between student and everyone studied by themselves.<br> It was a terrible circumstance—no-one wanted to help others with problems, consequently less advance between us. I felt uncertain about this phenomenon until I discovered an arcane academic term: involution, which has become shorthand used by Chinese urbanites to describe the ills of their modern lives and caused by the mentality of people who have turned apathetic by incessant competition.<br>With the deepening of understanding, I realized the real reason for this lack of teamwork: each student was very self-sufficient and self- absorbed and they perhaps felt threatened by newcomers and view this competition as negative to the development.<br>The issue first became apparent in the school clean-up which was tidying for the future mock exam. This is all very unclear and difficult to follow. Nevertheless, few people executed their tasks giving similar excuses of lethargy and indifference. I had a hunch that the teacher would be furious .However, our organizer was not angry or abused us for being lazy, on the contrary, she said a thought-provoking sentence : If everyone in the world only thought of themselves ,become selfish ,without helping, I am absolutely convinced that the result would be a disaster, none can afford.<br>On balance, keeping the classroom clean is not only the duty of the school’s cleaners but also everyone who spends in the classroom although it would take some time. Fortunately, our teacher corrected our poor behavior and gave us a very good example. In future group activities, more and more classmates prefer to give a helping hand because we have found that will improve life for everyone.</p>]]></content>
    
    
      
      
    <summary type="html">&lt;h2 id=&quot;Describe-an-accomplishment-event-or-realization-that-sparked-a-period-of-personal-growth-and-a-new-understanding-of-yourself-or-othe</summary>
      
    
    
    
    
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title></title>
    <link href="http://example.com/2022/01/29/%E7%AB%9E%E8%B5%9B%E5%A4%8D%E7%9B%98/"/>
    <id>http://example.com/2022/01/29/%E7%AB%9E%E8%B5%9B%E5%A4%8D%E7%9B%98/</id>
    <published>2022-01-29T17:13:27.236Z</published>
    <updated>2022-01-29T17:13:27.236Z</updated>
    
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<h1 id="竞赛复盘-截止至4-14"><a href="#竞赛复盘-截止至4-14" class="headerlink" title="竞赛复盘(截止至4.14)"></a>竞赛复盘(截止至4.14)</h1><ul><li><h2 id="UKMT复盘"><a href="#UKMT复盘" class="headerlink" title="UKMT复盘:"></a>UKMT复盘:</h2><ul><li><p>刷题3周，刷了5张卷子（2015，2016，2017，2018，2019）</p></li><li><p>和同学一起讨论题目（最后一排）</p></li><li><p><em><strong>考试中放掉一题未选，获得获得超级金奖（116）</strong></em></p><p><img                       lazyload                     src="/images/loading.svg"                     data-src="https://i.loli.net/2021/06/23/8LY1pGUVyEl4oC6.png"                      alt="UKMT"                ></p></li></ul></li><li><h2 id="BPHO复盘："><a href="#BPHO复盘：" class="headerlink" title="BPHO复盘："></a>BPHO复盘：</h2></li><li><p>有想选择有关物理专业的想法（可控核聚变）</p><ul><li>物理社的学长们给我们高一进行了培训（主要为数学知识）</li><li>准备：只是看了看卷子，高一只是熟悉一下考试，为以后拿大奖做准备</li><li>结果：铜奖2</li></ul></li></ul><p> <img                       lazyload                     src="/images/loading.svg"                     data-src="https://i.loli.net/2021/06/23/rqAxef9gW4B6Rsk.jpg"                      alt="BPho获奖证书.jpg"                ></p><ul><li><h2 id="AMC10-amp-12复盘："><a href="#AMC10-amp-12复盘：" class="headerlink" title="AMC10&amp;12复盘："></a>AMC10&amp;12复盘：</h2><ul><li>由于IG英语口语补习错过了许多课</li><li>详细学习有关面积和概率的题</li><li>注意时间安排，下次努力</li></ul></li><li><h2 id="Waterloo-Euclid"><a href="#Waterloo-Euclid" class="headerlink" title="Waterloo Euclid:"></a>Waterloo Euclid:</h2><ul><li>结果：全球前25% </li><li>由于Mock Exam，准备并不充分</li></ul></li></ul>]]></content>
    
    
      
      
    <summary type="html">&lt;h1 id=&quot;竞赛复盘-截止至4-14&quot;&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;#竞赛复盘-截止至4-14&quot; class=&quot;headerlink&quot; title=&quot;竞赛复盘(截止至4.14)&quot;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;竞赛复盘(截止至4.14)&lt;/h1&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;h2 id=&quot;UKMT复盘&quot;&gt;&lt;a hre</summary>
      
    
    
    
    
  </entry>
  
</feed>
